Guide to the Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015.]
Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015]
- Series IV. Videotapes
  - Subseries IVa. Videotapes transferred from Distributed Learning Services
    - CBE: Alumni interview and stream shot, October 29, 2007; V-2434; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - CBE: Archer (close), September 26, 2005; V-2435; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - CBE: Paulette Clancy, September 29, 2005; V-2436; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - CBE: Nanofab Clean Room, October 5, 2005; V-2437; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - CBE: Susan Daniel, December 17, 2007; V-2438; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - CBE: Hunter interview, November 5, 2007; V-2439; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - CBE: Prof. Lee, September 30, 2005; V-2440; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - CBE: Student/Professor interviews, September 14, 2005; V-2441; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - CBE: Varner classroom, November 14, 2005; V-2442; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Farm Link: Jeff Fetter and Judy Flint, July 24, 2006; V-2443; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Farm Link: Hayes Vineyard, October 30, 2006; V-2444 - V-2445; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Farm Link: Hazlitt Vineyard, July 26, 2005; V-2446; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Farm Link: Hazzlit Grape Harvest, October 8, 2006; V-2447; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Farm Link: Rus Hodnett, April 1, 2006; V-2448; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Farm Link: Eleanor Jacobs, October 4, 2006; V-2449; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Farm Link: [George Conneman] Patt Dairy Farm, July 28, 2006; V-2450; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Farm Link: George Conneman Patt Farm, November 14, 2006; V-2451; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Farm Link: Steve Richards interview, November 2, 2006; V-2452; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Farm Link: Ed Staehr, March 27, 2007; V-2453; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Farm Link: Virts Orchard, August 4, 2006; V-2454; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet Masters: J. Ashton, Farm Stress, V-2455; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet Masters: Mason Orchard, Farm Stress, V-2456; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet Masters: Van Bourgondien, V-2457; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet Masters: New York FarmNet Moving Families Forward, V-2458; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet Masters: Stress on the Farm, V-2459; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet: NY Farm Link - A Bridge Across the Generations, V-2460 - V-2461; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet: NY Farm Link - A Bridge Across the Generations with close captions, V-2462; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet: FarmNet 1 - David Call, Marc Smith at FarmNet meeting, June 13, 2005; V-2463; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet/Farm Link interviews: Wayne Knoblanch, Jane Magonigal, Steve Richards, August 1, 2005; V-2464; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet: Kellog goat farm, August 26, 2005; V-2465; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet: Brownell apple farm, September 28, 2005; V-2466 - V-2467; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet: John Brake, November 1, 2005; V-2468; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet Masters: New York FarmNet Moving Families Forward, V-2469; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet Masters: New York FarmNet Moving Families Forward with close captions, V-2470; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet: ORV: A Frontline Assault with close captions, V-2471; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet: Racheal, December 13, 2005; V-2472; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet: Ed Staehr, August 1, 2005; V-2473; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - FarmNet: Stress on the Farm with close captions, V-2474; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: Adventures in Living and Learning, 2008; V-2475; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: Calibrating the Falling Weight Deflectometer, V-2476; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: Chinampas segments, April 4, 2005; V-2477; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: "Cosmos," Rachel Bean, V-2478; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: Cybertower, Bruce Levitt, January 2005; V-2479; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: Dining Promo: "Be Charmed in Ithaca", March 2005; V-2480; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: Enriching the Cornell Experience, October 6, 2008; V-2481; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: Enriching the Cornell Experience, October 7, 2008; V-2482; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: Entrepreneurship Survey (English and Spanish), V-2483; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: "The Facts About Bats", November 2001; V-2484; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: The Facts About Bats... Exploring Conflicts and Designing Solutions, December 18, 2001; V-2485; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: Graduate Program in Chemical and Biomolecular Engineering, c. 1-2, October 7, 2008; V-2486; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: "How to Use Video In Your Presentations," David Lennox and Amy Newman, V-2487; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: "Loose Change," Name That Tune - United Way, V-2488; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: NCRI: Adventures in Living and Learning, 2005; V-2489; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: One Vision Many Voices: First Year Students Diversity Orientation, c. 1-2, V-2490; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: ORV Promo, March 19, 2004; V-2491; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: Oral Rabies Vaccination A Frontline Assault, 2006; V-2492; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - Masters: Welcome to Cornell: HR New Employee Orientation, 2003; V-2493; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - unidentified, V-2494; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 21)
    - ORV #1: Merial, April 19, 03; V-2495; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ORV #2: Merial, Joanne maki, Athens, GA, 2003; V-2496; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ORV #3: CDC, Chuck Ruppercht, May 20, 2003; V-2497; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ORV #4: CDC Atlanta, Cathleen Hanlon lab shots, May 20, 2003; V-2498; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ORV #5: CDC Atlanta, Dr. M. Meltzer, May 20, 2003; V-2499; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ORV: Ogdensburg, trapping/processing, October 8-9, 2003; V-2500 - V-2502; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ORV: Dennis Slate, V-2503; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ORV: Texas, February 23-25, 2004; V-2504 - V-2507; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ORV: Westport - helicopter, August 11, 2003; V-2508 - V-2509; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ORV: Westport - hand baiting, Health Dept. interview, August 12, 2003; V-2510; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ORV: Youngstown, Ohio, command post interviews: Ayers, Smith, September 11, 2003; V-2511; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ORV: Youngstown, Ohio, Twin Otter Bait drop, September 11, 2003; V-2512; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ORV: Youngstown, Ohio interviews: Sidwa, Hale, September 11, 2003; V-2513; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ORV: Youngstown, Ohio: Mentoney interview, loading baits; otter int[eraction (?)], pickups, takeoff, Slavitt interview; otter in flight, March 12, 2003; V-2514; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Cornell sign and students, September 14, 2004; V-2515; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - CBE - Martha Jones, V-2516; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - CBE international greetings, October 31, 2006; V-2517; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Sailing, September 13, 2005; V-2518; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Skiing - Greek Peak, January 4, 2008; V-2519; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Solar House, September 20, 2007; V-2520; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Traffic (on campus), January 25, 2008; V-2521; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Weill Medical School, NYC, October 26, 2006; V-2522; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Weill Hall, October 27, 2008; V-2523; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Welcome #4, Barnes, March 5, 2006; V-2524; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Welcome, Clarke interview, Deidre Collins, March 15, 2006; V-2525; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Welcome 2, Bill Alberts interview, March 22, 2006; V-2526; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Welcome, J. Rounds (Food Service), March 30, 2006; V-2527; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Welcome #5, GIAC, April 7, 2006; V-2528; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Welcome, Gannett, April 10, 2006; V-2529; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Clock Tower Chimes, April 13, 2006; V-2530; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Jazzercise/PT, April 17, 2006; V-2531; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Welcome, Willard Straight, April 19, 2006; V-2532; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Habitat for Humanity Volunteers, April 26, 2006; V-2533; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Welcome, Tatkon Center, April 28, 2006; V-2534; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Susan Murphy, May 10, 2006; V-2535; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Sue Parker, June 1, 2006; V-2536; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Cornell Dairy - exterior, July 31, 2006; V-2537; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - SAS: Catherine Holmes, Dean of Students, September 20, 2006; V-2538; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Cisco footage (dubbed from DVD), V-2539; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Commencement, Residence Halls, Tower Shot (from below), Ice Cream?, V-2540; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Coyote Damage Control in Rural and Urban Settings, produced by U. of Nebraska, 2003; CD-590; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - ASIF, Dr. Lisa Fortier Narration, February 23, 2009; CD-591; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Fubini Narration DVD 5, February 10, 2009; DVD-536; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Animation demo., Cubicomp software/ IBM Hard. P. Cavanaugh, V-2541; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - The Arecibo Observatory at the Cosmic Frontier, V-2542; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Blue Sky Below My Feet: Unit #3-Food and Nutrition (space food), V-2543; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - BUC$: Building an Understanding of Credit Services, V-2544; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Campus Spring '94: North Campus, McGraw Tower, Hec. Statue, Clock Tower, Ezra Statue, May 3, 1994; V-2545; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Child Care Focus Group: Child Care - A Key to Welfare Reform, October 1, 1996; V-2546; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Chyron titles only, S. Caldwell, V-2547; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - CNF Video Tour, 1998; V-2548; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Cornell vs. Bucknell: Kicking, c. 1-2, September 16, 2000; V-2549; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Deer Damage, V-2550; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Early Childhood Mentor: Isabel interview, April 16, 2002; V-2551; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Early Childhood Mentor Project, tape 2, November 2, 1999; V-2552; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - CEEM CNN tape - Fighting Potato Blight graphics (Chyron source tape), Dick Tenney, V-2553; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - 45th Reunion (June 1997), parts 1-4, June 1997; V-2554 - V-2555; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Gene Diversity in Zoo Populations, February 5, 1996; V-2556 - V-2557; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Jumpstart Keynote, tapes 1, 2, 4, June 2, 1998; V-2558 - V-2560; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Middle Childhood: Meeting the Needs of 5 to 8 Year Olds, V-2561; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - The Necropsy as Demonstrated by Dr. John King, Horse and Cow, V-2562; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Forestry, Forest Floor, Insects (Gypsy moths), Egrets (?) Flying, produced by Penn State Coll. of Agr. Sciences Agr. Info. Svcs., V-2563; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Purple Loosestrife, tape 1, digitized #4, July 26, 1995; V-2564; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Purple Loosestrife, tape 2, digitized #8, May 2, 1996; V-2565; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 22)
    - Hunter Rawlings Address for Von Retirement, June 29, 1999; V-2566; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Rearing of Biological Control Agents for Purple Loosestrife (backup), November 16, 1997; V-2567; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Restoring the Balance: Biological Control of Purple Loosestrife, July 1996; V-2568; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Robotic Soccer, produced by News Service, V-2569; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Sheep, T & R, "Tues," pasture, inside pens, windbreak, shearing, foraging in snow, January 13 - December 19, 1986; V-2570; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Sports: Scholar Athlete David Burke in class, January 31, 1990; V-2571; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Statler: Goodwin speech, tape 2, April 30, 1998; V-2572; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Statler: Anne Firor Scott, tapes 3-4, April 30, 1998; V-2573 - V-2574; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Statler: tape 5, April 30, 1998; V-2575; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Statler: Paul Brennan panel, tapes 6-7, April 30, 1998; V-2576 - V-2577; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Statler: tape 8, April 30, 1998; V-2578; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Statler: Moen and CRVIS panels, tapes 9-10, April 30, 1998; V-2579 - V-2580; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Titles (Chyron[?]), V-2581 - V-2582; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Training Development Seminar: Judith Ross-Bernstein, tapes 1, 2, 4, October 8, 1999; V-2583 - V-2585; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - You're Accountable (Spanish version), V-2586; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Zebra Mussels, Bill Lacy, December 15, 1994; V-2587; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Unidentified, V-2588 - V-2590; VHS (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Unidentified, V-2591 - V-2592; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Central Square Streets KFC, Beijing, China, Cam 1 tape 19, OFC140, January 5, 1989; V-2593; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Central Square and Streets of Beijing, Forbidden City, Cam 2 tape 20, OFC141, January 5, 1989; V-2594; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Beijing, China Peking Duck Dinner, Cam 2 tape 21, OFC142, January 5, 1989; V-2595; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Hong Kong APA Concept, Cam 1 tape 47, OFC168, January 14, 1989; V-2596; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Hong Kong APA Concept, Cam 1 tape 48, OFC169, January 14, 1989; V-2597; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Hong Kong APA Concept, Cam 1 tape 49, OFC170, January 14, 1989; V-2598; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Hong Kong APA Concept, Cam 1 tape 50, OFC171, January 14, 1989; V-2599; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Hong Kong City, Birds Central, Cam 1 tape 51, OFC172, January 16, 1989; V-2600; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Hong Kong City Tram, Cam 2 tape 52, OFC173, January 16, 1989; V-2601; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Hong Kong City (3) APA, Cam 2 tape 53, OFC174, produced by Star Kessy, January 16, 1989; V-2602; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Shanghai, China (Streets, U.S. Consulate, Morning Workouts), Cam 1 tape 54, OFC175, January 10, 1989; V-2603; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Shanghai - Streets, Cam 1 tape 16B, OFC33, produced by Li Ming, September 17, 1990; V-2604; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - University Murrow Plots, Purdue Univ. Ag-Sat Photos, Hatch 4, OFC177, July 4, 1990; V-2605; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Hello-California, Cam 1 Hatch 2, OFC37, April 7, 11-1986; V-2606; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Tree Planting/Mountains California, Hatch 4, OFC38, V-2607; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Purdue Uni. Growth Room, Sorghum Research, Corn Tables, Dolly, Hatch 5, OFC39, July 15, 1986; V-2608; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - South/West Lubbock, Texas, Hatch 8, OFC40, V-2609; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - S/W #4 Texas A&M Campus, Electron Microscope, Meat/PRGD, Hatch 11, OFC-41, June 6, 1986; V-2610; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 23)
    - Hatch 12, OFC42, June 9, 1986; V-2611; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - S/W #6 Catfish Research Station, Greenville, Miss., Hatch 13, OFC43, June 9, 1986; V-2612; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - S/W #9 Cotton Fields, Expert/Systems, Miss. University Computers, Hatch 14, OFC44, June 9, 1986; V-2613; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - S/W #8 Oglesby Plant Lab, Hatch 15, OFC45, June 12, 1986; V-2614; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Forest Decline Document-Acid Test Sites, #1 Chambers, OFC46, produced by McCune, August 31, 1987; V-2615; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Forest Decline: Trimming Trees in Chamber, tape 13, OFC70, September 14, 1988; V-2616; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Forest Decline: Snow on Chambers, tape 19, OFC71, February 7, 1989; V-2617; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - White Face Mt., tape 1, OFC72; tape 2, OFC73, October 11 - 12, 1988; V-2618 - V-2619; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Boyce Tompson Gypse Moths, OFC74, October 25; V-2620; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - BTI: Alaskan Tundra & Oil Refineries, OFC75, March 12, 1991; V-2621; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Chopper Shots CA Lakes and Forest, More Green, OFC76, V-2622; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - State Fair 1986, OFC01, December 20, 1991; V-2623; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Econ Outlook Open: House Construction & For Sale, OFC02, May 20, 1991; V-2624; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Wetlands Longstorm Landfill, OFC05, July 24, 1990; V-2625; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Wetlands Longstorm Landfill tape #2, OFC08, October 10, 1991; V-2626; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Wetlands N. Fenton Landfill, OFC07, July 10, 1990; V-2627; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Wetlands Fenton Landfill, OFC06, October 8, 1991; V-2628; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Wetlands Ithaca Waste Water Treatment Plant, OFC09, April 13, 1992; V-2629; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Emily "Live" Sat. Down Link-N.C. Coast 3:50 PM, OFC176, August 3, 1993; V-2630; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Pathogens Narration, V-2631; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Pathogens, V-2632; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Willsboro Research Narration, V-2633; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Bob Earle Narration, May 22, 1996; V-2634; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - Watershed Music, 1996; V-2635; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - CCESN IN-Services: Update on Legal Issues in Child Protective Services, tapes 1-2, September 15, 1998; V-2636 - V-2637; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - CCESN In-services: HUD Healthy Homes Initiative, March 29, 2000; V-2638; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - CCESN In-services: HUD Healthy Homes Initiative, March 29, 2000; V-2639; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - CCESN In-services: Building Board Capacity Air Master, tapes 1-2, February 9, 1999; V-2640 - V-2641; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - CCESN In Services: Coalescing Community Health Issues, SAT72-SAT73, Tapes 1-2, October 11, 1994; V-2642 - V-2643; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - CCESN In-Services: CCE Statewide Connection Air Master, October 6, 1999; V-2644; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - CCESN In-Services: Targeting and Prioritizing Water Quality Problems, SAT93, tape 1, February 14, 1995; V-2645; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 24)
    - CCESN In-Services: Targeting and Prioritizing Water Quality Problems, SAT94-SAT95, Tapes 2-3, February 14, 1995; V-2646 - V-2647; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - CCESN In-Services: Why Some Children Seem to Misrepresent Events, Tapes 1-2, April 27, 1999; V-2648 - V-2649; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - CCESN In-Services: Power Systems Seminars Fractals in Power System Load Flows w/Akbar Naqavi PHD, SAT76, October 17, 1994; V-2650; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - CCESN In-Services: Power System Seminar w/ John Guckenheimer, SAT79, November 28, 1994; V-2651; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - CCESN In-Services: 1995 Agribusiness Situation and Outlook, SAT91-SAT92, Tapes 1-2, January 24, 1995; V-2652 - V-2653; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - CCESN In-Services: Biotech in Your Backyard, SAT74-SAT75 Tapes 1-2, April 2, 1993; V-2654 - V-2655; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - CCESN In-Services: Biodiversity for Farms and Forests, SAT80, October 13, 1994; V-2656; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - CCESN In-Services: 4H Strategic Planning, February 15, 2000; V-2657; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - CCESN In-Services: Zebra Mussels Teleconference, SAT82, tape 1, December 20, 1994; V-2658; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - CCESN In-Services: Collaborative Approaches to Small Business Training, June 2, 1998; V-2659; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - CCESN In-Services: What's Going On with West Nile Virus, No date; V-2660; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - (Box 35-14-3773 - Air Master?)
    - CCESN In-Services: Safe and Supportive Communities, June 2, 1999; V-2661; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - CCESN In-Services: National Forum on Life Cycles and Volunteering, May 1, 1998; V-2662; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - Bugs Actors, tapes 1-2, October 3, 1988; V-2663 - V-2664; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - Entomology Bug Shoot Tapes 1-2, September 26, 1988; V-2665 - V-2666; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - Entomology "Bugs" Kitchen Tapes 1-3, July 29, 1988; V-2667 - V-2669; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 25)
    - Entomology "Bugs" Air Fly-By Tapes 1-2, July 28, 1988; V-2670 - V-2671; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - Entomology More Egypt and China, February 1, 1989; V-2672; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - Insect Art, tapes 1-2, V-2673 - V-2674; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - Entomology Raid Off-NASA/Egypt, February 1, 1989; V-2675; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - Electron U-Scope, V-2676; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - Bugs- Female Actor POND, October 19, 1988; V-2677; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - Raid Historical, V-2678; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - Entomology Coins and Candle, V-2679; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - Bugs, house, tape 3, December 6, 1988; V-2680; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - Bugs, basement, tape 4, December 6, 1988; V-2681; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - Entomology Bug Graphics, October 31, 1988; V-2682; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - Horse Barns, tapes 1-3, 1988; V-2683 - V-2685; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - WIXT News & Locust, January 29, 1989; V-2686; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - IBM Bughouse Demo Tapes 1-2, June 2, ??; V-2687 - V-2688; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - El Teatro, tapes 2-3, September 20, 1989; V-2689 - V-2690; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)
    - The Winners Film Dub Entomology, February 1, 1989; V-2691; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 26)